perksatwork.com 2017-06-14

# Privacy Policy - L3 Technologies Perks at Work

L3 Technologies Perks at Work Privacy Policy (Last Updated on 05/10/17) 

Next Jump ("Next Jump", "We", "Us" or "Our") is committed to your privacy. This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") is meant to help you understand what data we collect, how we use that data and the choices we offer you, including how to access and update your information. 

We provide you with a program that aggregates the purchasing power of millions of individuals in order to create special pricing on a wide range of goods and services ("Program"). As a registered user of the Program, you will have access to the following features: 

  * ONECart: ability to make purchases directly through the Programme;
  * WOWPoints: ability to earn and burn reward currency WOWPoints (100 WOWPoints = $1 [USD], or £1 [GBP] for UK users) at hundreds of retailers;
  * In Store Rewards: ability to shop in-store using your own credit or debit card and earn WOWPoints;
  * Shopping Cards: ability to purchase pre-paid shopping cards and instant e-codes; and
  * Reward & Recognition or WOWCards: WOWPoints given to you as part of the Programme;

We ensure that your personal data is processed in accordance with relevant laws and industry-recognized data protection standards. At no time will We trade, sell, or distribute your personal information to any individual, company, vendor or organization, in ways other than disclosed in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or concerns regarding Our Privacy Policy, please contact Us through one of the methods described below. 

By registering for the Program, you acknowledge that you have read this Privacy Policy and consent to the practices described herein, including the transfer of your personal information to entities outside the country of origin. To be clear, we store your personal information on servers located in the United States of America. By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you give your consent for us to do so. 

We collect information for the purposes of authenticating your right to use the Program, optimizing your experience, conducting financial transactions, tracking your transaction activity at retailers in order to provide WOWPoints, and providing you with customer service. We do not collect information that is irrelevant to the purpose of providing you with access to or use of the Program. We collect the following information: 

  * The required information is your first name, last name, email address, and postal code, which are the only data that you must provide to use the Program ("Required Information"). As an eligible member of the Program, some or all of the Required Information may be provided to Us by your organization. By registering for the Program, you are directly providing Us with the Required Information and giving us your consent to use it as set out in this Privacy Policy. 
  * The additional personal information is the information that you may decide to voluntarily provide Us in order for Us to allow you to use additional functionality in the Program ("Additional Information"). Additional information includes: 
    * Preferences and reminders
    * Friends and family contact information
    * Address
    * Date of Birth
    * Payment and bank account information
  * The information automatically generated while you use the Program ("Automatically Generated Information") includes: 
    * Transactional information
    * Customer service inquiries
    * WOWPoints activity
    * Clickstream information
    * Cookies
    * Shopping information like travel itineraries, e-codes, and cinema codes created as a result of using the Programme

We use the information We collect for the following purposes: 

  * The Required Information is used to (i) verify your affiliation with your organization, (ii) authenticate you to a unique account, (iii) communicate with you, and (iv) enable you to access the benefits and services of the Program.
  * The Additional Information is used to (i) facilitate additional functionality, (ii) fulfill transactions.
  * The Automatically Generated Information is used by Us to (i) provide you with customer service, (ii) operate your organization or employer's Rewards and Recognition Program, (iii) affect session management, and (iv) respond to your requests.
  * All Information collected is also used to (i) protect you, (ii) prevent fraud, (iii) provide relevant offers, and (iv) optimize your experience.

Information about you is an important part of Our business. We do not sell your information to any third parties. All information disclosing is based on the principle of sharing only the information necessary to fulfill the legitimate business purpose. When shared, data may be transferred and hosted outside the country of origin. 

  * Aggregated information showing the general use of the Program without any personally identifying information is shared with your organization to evaluate the effectiveness and value of the Program; 
  * Information on whether and when you have registered and used the Program may be provided to your organization to minimize redundant or irrelevant communications; 
  * Information on spending and savings on the Program may be provided to your organization to be included in total reward statements with other benefits you receive from your organization; 
  * Information about your WOWPoints activity may be provided to your organisation to facilitate the operation of long service and, rewards and recognition;
  * RSVPs for private, in store events may be provided to participating vendors for admittance to the event;
  * Payment card information may be shared with payment processors to facilitate card transactions and identify transactions where you have earned or burned WOWPoints;
  * Bank account information may be shared with our bank to facilitate payment into your account;
  * Information may be shared with participating merchants in order to fulfill your purchase transaction, including payment information, shipping address and other personal information that may be required to complete such transaction; 
  * If your organisation has contracted a third party to run the Programme (such as a flexible benefits provider), any of the above information We share with your organisation may also be shared with the third party;
  * All of the information we collect, as described above, may be shared with the companies that perform the IT services on Our behalf such as credit card processors, data management firms, data analytics firms, fraud prevention services and call center providers for the purposes of providing you with the Program and developing and maintaining it. 

In the event Next Jump discloses Personal Data covered by this Policy to a non-agent third party, it will do so consistent with any notice provided to Data Subjects and any choice they have exercised regarding such disclosure. If Next Jump has knowledge that a third party to which it has disclosed Personal Data covered by this Policy is processing such Personal Data in a way that is contrary to this Policy and/or the Principles, Next Jump will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop such processing. In such case, the third-party is liable for damages unless it is proven that Next Jump is responsible for the event giving rise to the violation. 

We are committed to protecting the confidentiality of your information. We take reasonable measures to secure your information, including industry standard administrative, physical and technical controls. These controls include encryption, third party audits, access controls and security testing. 

We use cookies to provide you with the best experience while using the Program, to manage your browser sessions and to power the Program's functionality. Cookies allow you to use all of the Program's functions as designed. Disabling cookies will limit functionality of the Program and significantly degrade the user experience. 

Some third parties (e.g., advertisers, tracking utilities) use cookies and Web beacons on their site(s). We do not have access or control over these tracking technologies. We do not share your personally identifiable data with these advertisers. 

This Privacy Policy covers Our use of cookies on the Program and the private label subdomains delivered by Us, only. This Privacy Policy notice does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties. 

Because We provide the Program worldwide, this may involve Us transferring your information to countries whose data protection laws differ from the laws of the originating country. 

With the exception of pre-registration emails, We do not send you unsolicited emails without your consent. We send pre-registration emails at the request of your organization. You may choose to receive correspondence, including email reminders, newsletters and Program updates using the "My Account" section of the Program. 

All emails sent by Us relating to the Programme contain instructions on how to unsubscribe from future correspondence. You may opt out of correspondence relating to the Programme by visiting the [Contact Us](https://www.perksatwork.com/help/contact/uSource/UKPP) page. Users may also access and edit their personal information in the "My Account" section of the website. 

If you would like your personal information, including email address, to be completely removed from Our database, you should use the [Contact Us](https://www.perksatwork.com/help/contact/uSource/UKPP) page. We will respond to your request within ten (10) business days. Completely removing your personal information from the database will negate your ability to login and use to the Program. 

You are entitled to request a copy of your personal information held by Us, as well as a description of how the information is used. A Subject Access Request should be made using the [Contact Us](https://www.perksatwork.com/help/contact/uSource/UKPP) page. 

To comply with the Standard Contractual Clauses (model contracts issued by the EU Commission for data transfers outside of the European Economic Area), We may need to notify and obtain authorization from your organization prior to responding to any data subject access request. 

This Privacy Policy may be reviewed and amended from time to time. You will be notified of changes to this Privacy Policy by a notice posted on the Program login page. The notice will contain a link, whereby the amended privacy policy can be examined in full. In this way, you will be made aware of policy changes prior to browsing or shopping on the Program. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check Our website frequently to see recent changes. As always, if you are not amenable to the conditions of a revised privacy policy you may opt out of the Program by the means outlined earlier in the 'Opting Out' section above. 

Many offers on the Programme will redirect you to a participating retailer's web site. An interstitial page will be displayed that will inform you that you are being redirected. At this point you will be on the merchant web site and the merchant's privacy policy will now apply to any information you provide. It is important to read and familiarise yourself with the merchant's privacy policy. 

Although your privacy is of paramount concern to Us, we cannot reasonably be expected to suppress information where the withholding of such information is a violation of law. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information, to your organization or authorities, as required by law and when it is believed that disclosure is necessary to protect Our rights, our clients' interests and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. 

If You have questions or concerns regarding this statement or the Programme, You should submit your enquiry through the [Contact Us](https://www.perksatwork.com/help/contact/uSource/UKPP) page. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you may initiate a dispute resolution process. If you are a citizen of the European Economic Area, you should contact the European Union Data Protection Authorities Panel (EU DPA) on ec-dppanel-secr@ec.europa.eu. The EU DPA will then serve as a liaison to resolve your concerns. 

If you are not a citizen of the European Economic Area, you should contact the U.S. Better Business Bureau [http://www.BBB.org](http://www.bbb.org/). The Better Business Bureau will then serve as a liaison to resolve your concerns. 

Next Jump is committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, trade, give away, or rent personal information to any third parties in ways other than disclosed in this privacy statement. We use the information collected while you are using the Program in order to make shopping and promotional activities possible and enhance your overall experience of the Program. 

We provide several methods for corresponding with us. Please direct your questions or comments to: 

  * [Contact Us](https://www.perksatwork.com/help/contact/uSource/UKPP) page
  * Postal mail can be sent to:  
ATTN: Customer Service Department  
Next Jump Limited  
99 Waterloo Road  
London  
SE1 8XP 
  * For All other users, Postal Mail to:  
ATTN: Customer Service Department  
Next Jump Inc.  
9261 5th Avenue 8th Floor  
New York, NY 10016, U.S.A.
